aviationcareer.com 2002-11-05

# Aviation Career Magazine - Privacy Policy

_**AviationCareer.net**_ has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.aviationcareer.net. 

Our site's registration forms require users to give us contact information (such as their email address). We use this contact information from the registration forms to transmit our weekly newsletter, and also to send the users other relevant information. This information may be also used to contact the user if that becomes necessary. We may also collect demographic information in order to allow us to refine our website and newsletter to better serve our audience. Any information provided is at the users' own option. 

We do not release individual user data to any third parties. The demographic and profile data that are collected at our site may be made available to others on an aggregate basis only (e.g. we may provide information such as "70% of our users are located in the United States"), but we do not release information that is specific to a single user. 

**Cookies**

Our ad serving system may use a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a random number user ID that the site assigns to a visitor to track the pages they have visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

Cookies allows us to measure and report aggregate information to site advertisers such as the number of people who see their ad (reach) and the number of times people see their ad (frequency). They also allow us to deliver ads that are more relevant to visitors and avoid delivering the same ads too many times to one visitor. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. Our ad serving program will only store information provided voluntarily, but this information is not personally identifiable. 

If for some reason you would rather not take advantage of the benefits made possible by cookies, most browsers allow you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept. 

**Opt-In**

E-mails sent from AviationCareer.net will only be sent to addresses of individuals who have requested to receive them, or to addresses of individuals who have registered at other websites within the AviationCareer.net family and have expressed a desire to receive aviation employment related information. 

**Opt-out**

This site gives users the option for removing themselves from our mailing list, which is accomplished by entering the e-mail address to be removed at <http://www.aviationcareer.net/newsletter/management.cfm>. It the responsibility of the user to supply the correct e-mail address on this form. 

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms and bulletin boards available to its users, or provides links to them. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. If you post to such a forum and disclose your personal information or e-mail address publicly, you should understand that doing so makes your information available to all users. If after posting to a public forum you are approached by a third party by email, do not assume that we have released private information about you. It is our strict policy to never sell or redistribute the email addresses of our members to any third parties; however in posting a message to a public forum, you are in essence releasing your own information publicly. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the website, or your dealings with the website, you can contact:

AviationCareer.net  
P.O. Box 550070   
Ft Lauderdale, FL 33355   
Phone: 954-472-6684   
Or e-mail to [editor@aviationcareer.net](mailto:editor@aviationcareer.net)
